Inventory of the Papers of Monroe Leigh, 1941 - 2001
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Personal Papers
  - University of Virginia Student Materials
    - [International Law Notebook]? ca. 1941 - 1947 (Box-folder 54 - 1)
      Contains a couple of pages of handwritten notes. Added to collection / Donated in 2005.
    - Student Notebook - Contracts [Dillard], Quiz and Exam [Sep - Dec] 1941, 1946 (Box-folder 54 - 2)
    - Student Notebook - Torts 1, Term Paper [Buckler] [Sep - Dec] 1941 (Box-folder 54 - 3)
    - Law Student Notebook - Torts 2 Jan - March 1942 (Box-folder 54 - 4)
    - Law Student Notebook - Equity (Glenn, Virginia Procedure (Nash) [March] - June 1942, March - June 1946 (Box-folder 54 - 5)
    - Law Student Notebook - Criminal Law, Legal History (summer session, Wed - Sat) & Legal History Exam [1941], July - Sept. 1942 (Box-folder 54 - 6)
    - Law Student Notebook - Contracts [Dillard], Securities [Glenn] 1942, Sep - Oct 21, 1942 (Box-folder 55 - 1)
    - Law Student Notebook - Admiralty [White] Sept - Dec 1942 (Box-folder 55 - 2)
    - Law Student Notebook - Conflict of Laws Sept - Dec 1942 (Box-folder 55 - 3)
    - Law Student Notebook - Evidence Feb - June 1946 (Box-folder 55 - 4)
    - Law Student Notebook - Corporate Finance, Legal History Summer 1946 (Box-folder 55 - 5)
    - Contracts Paper - In the Supreme Court of the State of Minor Corn Husk Co. v. Universal Pig-Sty Assoc. Dec 1941 - Feb 1942 (Box-folder 56 - 1)
    - Warranty Deed, Quitclaim Deed 1945, 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 2)
    - Law Student Notes - Constitutional Law ca. 1964 (Box-folder 56 - 3)
    - Law Student Notes - Contracts, Arbitration ca. 1941 - 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 4)
    - Law Student Notes, [Creditors' Rights], Glenn ca. 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 5)
    - Law Student Notes - Federal Jurisdiction and Procedure ca. 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 6)
    - Law Student Notes - Foreign Commercial Transactions [ca. Sept - Dec] 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 7)
    - Law Student Notes - Virginia Constitution and Statutes RE: Militia ca. 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 8)
    - Lectures on Trial Practice Court by Oscar W. Underwood, Jr. 1946 (Box-folder 56 - 9)